Chicago Ethnic Arts Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 7: Graphic Materials, 1977
  - Subseries 1: Color slides and negatives
    - Korean Americans
      - Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush artist, Chicago; home of Mr. Jae K. Lee, Chicago, Illinois, June 24, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50898; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-11, Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush artist, 6244 N. Claremont, Chicago; 12-13, closet for the storage of scrolls; 14, scroll; 15-21, in the home of Mr. Jae K. Lee, 6225 N. Claremont, Mrs. Lee and unidentified child; 22-36, examples of lacquered wood furniture inlaid with mother-of-pearl brought from Korea.
      - Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush artist, Chicago, Illinois, June 24, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50899; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 2-3, artist's materials at the home of Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush artist, 6244 N. Claremont, Chicago, 4-6, 24-25, brush painting; 7-23, 30-31, Mr Park at work; 26-29, painted fan; 32-33, artist's materials; 34-35, coloring materials; 36, Mr. Park.
      - Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Chicago, Illinois, July 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b51720; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-4, 16-19, Indian Temple Dance (East India) at the Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival; 5-15, 21, 36-37, audience; 22-29, Korean dancers preparing for their dance; 30-35, Korean dancers on stage.
      - Lyman Pierce, Illinois (Indian) Employment and Training Center; Mr. Kean Sea Park, brush artist; Little Village neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b72637; Jonas Dovydenas; 33 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
      - Children's folktale contest and old people's birthday party, held at Shinsundo Studio, 3315 N. Clark St., Chicago, Illinois, 1977, AFC 1981/004: ch2; Chungmoo Choi; 4 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: black and white copy negatives of color slides 8 and 15 in the set at call number AFC 1981/004: 142; the images are from the Korean American children's folktale contest and old people's birthday party held at Shinsundo (Shin Sun Do) Studio, 3315 N. Clark St., Chicago, also the Korean Forum (a service organization for American-Asians); frames 1-2 (identical images), I-uk Chung, tells story of, "village of the good son"; 3-4 (identical images), guests and audience at the birthday party, the fieldworked noted that men and women were seated separately on the floor, with most men wearing western style clothing and most women in Korean costume or Korean version of western style dress.
    - Japanese Americans
      - Fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada, Sonny, and John, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 150; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada (Okada?), Sonny, and John, fieldworker Chungmoo Choi is wearing red jacket in image 19.
      - Fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada, Sonny, and John, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 151; Jonas Dovydenas; 18 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada (Okada?), Sonny, and John; 1-3, Butch, Sonny, and John, 4-15, catching and landing a fish; 16-18, Sonny with the fish.
      - Japanese dancing instruction, Chicago Buddhist Temple, 1151 W. Leland, Chicago, Illinois, June 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 152; Jonas Dovydenas; 17 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-17, Japanese dancing instruction, Chicago Buddist Temple, 1151 W. Leland, Chicago; folk dance rehearsal for performance at Natsu Matsuri (Summer Festival) to be held July 2-3, 1977, at the temple.
      - Flower arranging class held by Mrs. Mary Higeko Hamano, Chicago, Illinois, June 23, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 157; Jonas Dovydenas; 10 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-5, at a flower arranging class held by Mrs. Mary Higeko Hamano, 2921 N. Halstead, Chicago, Mrs. Hamano, at right, with students; 6-8, student at work; 9-10, arrangement with daffodils.
      - Japanese tea ceremony at the home of Rev. and Mrs. Gyomay M. Kubose, Chicago, Illinois, June 26, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 165; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-2, Japanese tea ceremony at home of Rev. Gyomay M. Kubose and his wife Mine ("Minnie") Somi Kubose, 4635 N. Racine, Chicago, participants: Ms. Joyce Kubose Evans, hostess (cream kimono), Ms. Peggy Tokimoto, second guest (blue kimono), Mrs. Sobi Kubose, main guest (dark kimono); 3-4, hostess brings in sweet, okashi, to guests; 5-6, hostess begins to prepare tea; 7, bowl of sweets; 8-10, guests begin to eat sweets; 11-13, hostess prepares tea; 14-15, guest looks at tea making equipment; 16-20, posing for picture.
      - Fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada, Sonny, and John, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49873; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-4, fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada (Okada?), Sonny, and John, fishing boat on the lake; 5-8, John; 9, Chungmoo Choi (fieldworker), Butch; 10-11, Sonny; 12-13, John, Sonny; 14-15, John; 16-17, Sonny, Butch; 18-22, L-r, Sonny, John, Butch; 23-24, 27, 33-36, John; 25-26, the boat; 28-32, Sonny, Butch.
      - Japanese dancing instruction, Chicago Buddhist Temple, 1151 W. Leland, Chicago, Illinois, June 19, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49874; Jonas Dovydenas; 37 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-36, Japanese dancing instruction at the Chicago Buddist Temple, 1151 W. Leland, Chicago, folk dance rehearsal for performance at Natsu Matsuri (Summer Festival), to be held July 2-3, 1977, at the temple.
      - View of Chinatown; Fishing on Lake Michigan, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49877; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-10, scenes of Korean and other Asian shops and organizations in Chinatown near S. Wentworth Ave.; 11-36, preparing for fishing trip on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada (Okada?), Sonny, and John, at diner, on the dock; 16a, Butch; 17, 19-20, Sonny, John; 18, John; 21-22, Sonny; 23-25, boat on the trailer; 26-27, launching the boat; 28, Sonny, Butch; 29, John, Butch; 30-32, John, Chungmoo Choi (fieldworker); 33, John, Sonny, Butch; 34, fishing poles; 35, Sonny, Butch; 36, John, Sonny, Butch.
      - Fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada, Sonny, and John, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49878; Jonas Dovydenas; 36 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-22, fishing trip on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada (Okada?), Sonny, and John, with fieldworker Chungmoo Choi; 23-29, after the fishing trip; 30-36, unidentified.
      - Fishing on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada, Sonny, and John, Chicago, Illinois, June 18, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50877; Jonas Dovydenas; 38035 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1, fishing trip on Lake Michigan with Butch Okkada (Okada?), left to right, Sonny, Butch, and John; 2-3, Sonny, John; 4-6, Chungmoo Choi, fieldworker; 7-8, Sonny, Chungmoo Choi; 9, Butch, John; 10, Butch, John, Chungmoo Choi; 11-13, Chungmoo Choi, Sonny; 14, lunch box, traditional Japanese foods; 15, Sonny, Chungmoo Choi; 16, Chungmoo Choi, John; 17-21, landing a fish; 22-23, Sonny with the fish; 24-35, Butch landing fish; 36-37, Sonny.
      - Japanese tea ceremony at the home of Rev. and Mrs. Gyomay M. Kubose, Chicago, Illinois, June 26, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50878; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-6, Japanese tea ceremony at home of Rev. Gyomay M. Kubose and his wife Mine ("Minnie") Somi Kubosi, 4645 N. Racine, Chicago; second guest starts eating sweets (fieldworker's notes based in interviews indicates that eating sweets must precede drinking tea because the sweetness enhances the relatively bitter taste of tea that follows); 7, Chungmoo Choi, fieldworker, looks on; 8-12, second guest goes and gets tea; 13-14, second guest drinks tea; 15, after drinking the tea, the guest admires the art of the tea bowl (chawan) - not a cup, a cup is smaller; 16, returns the bowl; 17, main guest asks to see the tea caddy (natsume), lacquered container with the fine green powder (tea) and the tea scoop (chashaku); 18-21, cleaning the items to present them; 22, presenting the items; 24, hostess leaves room; 25, hostess brings fresh water in mizutsugi; 26, shows mitzutsugi; 27-31, hostess has gone to replenish water being heated; guests closely observing and chashaku (fieldworker's notes based in interviews indicates that this should not be occurring); 32, waiting for return of hostess; 33, hostess returns; "such beautiful art,” she tells about tea caddy and scoop; 34, answering - ''nice combination”; 35, "Thank you," it is always the main guest who speaks; 36, removes items, 37, hostess thanks guests for coming.
      - Particpants in the Japanese tea ceremony at the home of Rev. and Mrs. Gyomay M. Kubose, Chicago, Illinois, June 26, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50882; Jonas Dovydenas; 39 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-8, participants in Japanese tea ceremony at home of Rev. Gyomay M. Kubose and his wife Mine ("Minnie") Somi Kubosi, 4645 N. Racine, Chicago include Mrs. Sobi M. Kubose, Ms. Peggy N. Tokimoto, Ms. Joyce Kubose Evans (Joyce Kubose); 9-12, Rev. Gyomay M. Kubose on left; 12-16, Kubose family; 17-22, Ms. Peggy N. Tokimoto, Ms. Joyce Kubose Evans (Joyce Kubose); 23-31, Mrs. Kubose making tea (the fieldworker's notes, based on interviews, indicates that 23 and 24 are incorrect moves); 32-36, Joyce Kubose Evans putting on sash with help from Ms. Tokimoto.
      - Japanese tea ceremony at the home of Rev. and Mrs. Gyomay M. Kubose, Chicago, Illinois, June 26, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50890; Jonas Dovydenas; 39 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-1, observing the scroll in door at the Japanese tea ceremony at home of Rev. Gyomay M. Kubose and his wife Mine ("Minnie") Somi Kubosi, 4645 N. Racine, Chicago; 2-5, posing for picture, participants: Ms. Joyce Kubose Evans (Joyce Kubose), hostess (light kimono); Ms. Peggy Tokimoto, second guest (medium kimono); Mrs. Sobi Kubose, main guest (dark kimono); 6-8, hostess brings in sweet, okashi, to guests; 9, hostess brings in utensils to make tea; 10-25, preparing the tea; 26-30, as tea is prepared, guest begins to eat sweets; 31-33, waiting for tea; 34, main guest excuses herself to second guest for being the first to drink tea; 35, main guest thanks hostess for making tea; 36-37, main guest drinks the tea.
      - Flower arranging class held by Mrs. Mary Higeko Hamano, Chicago, Illinois, June 23, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50891; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-36, at the flower arranging (ikebana) class held by Mrs. Mary Higeko Hamano, 2921 N. Halstead, Chicago, Mrs. Hamano and unidentified students; 4, Mrs. Hamano; 10, Chungmoo Choi, fieldworker, left.
      - Japanese kimono at the home of Rev. and Mrs. Gyomay M. Kubose, Chicago, Illinois, June 26, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b50897; Jonas Dovydenas; 35 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-25, Ms. Joyce Kubosi Evans removing kimono with help of Ms. Peggy Tokimoto and Chungmoo Choi, fieldworker; 26, Chungmoo Choi, Mrs. Sobi Kubose; 27, Chungmoo Choi, Mine ("Minnie") Somi Kubose and her husband the Rev. Gyomay M. Kubose; 28-34, Mrs. Kubose modelling kimono.
      - Japanese Buddhist Temple Street Fair, Chicago, Illinois, July 02, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52025; Jonas Dovydenas; 39 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-34, Japanese Buddhist Temple Street Fair, W. Leland Ave; 35-37, unidentified girl with tattoo on her arm.
    - Asian Americans
      - Chicago's Chinatown near S. Wentworth Ave., Chicago, Illinois, June 17 - June 18, 1977, June 17, 1977; AFC 1981/004: 143; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, scenes of Chinatown near S. Wentworth Ave and 23d St. 17-20, Pui Tak Center (former On Leong Building).
      - Chicago's Chinatown near S. Wentworth Ave.; Korean and other Asian shops and organizations in the Lakewood neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, June 17 - June 18, 1977, June 17, 1977; AFC 1981/004: 144; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-5, scenes of Pui Tak Center in Chinatown near S. Wentworth Ave and 23d St.; 6-8, skull in car window with sticker with word Mexico on windshield, exact location unknown; 9-10, decorated doorway, exact location unknown; 11, Longevity Health Clinic street scene (probably on N. Clark St.); 12-14, Chinatown including identifying plaque; 15-20, scenes of Arirang Food Mart (Korean) on N. Clark St. in or near the 3300-3400 block.
      - Korean and other Asian shops and organizations in the Lakewood neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, June 17 - June 18, 1977, June 17, 1977; AFC 1981/004: 145; Jonas Dovydenas; 19 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, scenes of Korean and other Asian shops and organizations on N. Clark St. in or near the 3300-3400 block. 11-12, upper portion of exterior façade of Shinsundo (Shin Sun Do) Studio, 3315 N. Clark St., Chicago.
      - Korean and other Asian shops and organizations in the Lakewood neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, June 17 - June 18, 1977, June 17, 1977; AFC 1981/004: 146; Jonas Dovydenas; 19 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, scenes of the interior of an Asian food store in on N. Clark St. on or near the 3300-3400 block.
      - Korean and other Asian shops and organizations in the Lakewood neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, June 17 - June 18, 1977, June 17, 1977; AFC 1981/004: 147; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, scenes of Korean and other Asian shops and organizations on N. Clark St. on or near the 3300-3400 block; 3-4, exterior of Sam Mee Korean Restaurant, 3370 N. Clark St.
      - Korean and other Asian shops and organizations in the Lakewood neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, June 17 - June 18, 1977, June 17, 1977; AFC 1981/004: 148; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, scenes of Korean and other Asian shops and organizations on N. Clark St. on or near the 3300-3400 block; 1-4, exterior façade of Shinsundo (Shin Sun Do) Studio, 3315 N. Clark St., Chicago; 5-6, Pan International Travel (Chicago to Seoul travel is highlighted); 8-9, Mike Art Studio (photography).
      - Korean and other Asian shops and organizations in the Lakewood neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, June 17 - June 18, 1977, June 17, 1977; AFC 1981/004: 149; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, scenes of Korean and other Asian shops and organizations on N. Clark St. on or near the 3300-3400 block; 1-3, exterior façade, of Korea Food Market; 4-6, Latino-style wall mural on Sheffield, at Clark; 7-8, exterior of Lantern Korean Restaurant; 9-20, Manna Oriental Foods façade, sign, and show windows.
      - Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Chicago, Illinois, July 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 166; Jonas Dovydenas; 19 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-2, at the Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Indian dancer before performance; 3-11, Indian Temple Dance; 12-16, Asian Forum; Shin Sun Do (Shin-sun-Do, Shinsundo), world peace through a program of physical exercise; 17-19, spectators.
      - Japanese Buddhist Temple Street Fair, Chicago, Illinois, July 02, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 167; Jonas Dovydenas; 12 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-10, at the Japanese Buddist Temple Street Fair, Racine and W. Leland Ave., Chicago; performers (Hawaiian? Sign says “Kauai Surf Riders”) on stage, different groups also portrayed with no change in signage; 11, woman in costume that includes lei (?)
      - Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Chicago, Illinois, July 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 168; Jonas Dovydenas; 19 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-13, at the Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Korean dancers on stage; 14-19, Filipino dancers.
      - Garden of Roberto and Amelia Leval, Chicago; Manna Oriental Food Store, Chicago, Illinois, August 22, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 71987; Jonas Dovydenas; 12 2 ¼ x 2 ¼ in. in. black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-9, garden of Roberto and Amelia Leval, 1515 W. Berteau, Chicago; the Levals are a retired Cuban couple and their garden has vegetables, flowers (plastic and real), and animal figures, windmills, and a madonna; 10-11, Manna Oriental Food Store; 12, unidentified children.
      - Lithuanian birbyne ensemble, Chicago, Illinois; Mr. Antanas Poskocimas, woodcarver, Chicago, Illinois; Street scenes of Chinatown, Chicago, Illinois,, June 14, 1977; June 17, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b49879; Jonas Dovydenas; 34 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-3, Balys Pakstas' birbyne ensemble, left to right, Mr. Vincus Vaitkus (Vaitkevicius), Mr. Liubomiras Bichnevicius, Mr. Balys Pakstas; 5-8, Antanas Poskocimas, center, with neighbors; 10-15, Woodcarving by Mr. Poskocimas; 16-29, views of shops in Chinatown near S. Wentworth Ave. and 23d Street, fieldworker Chungmoo Choi in frame 16. 4, 9, 19-27, and 30-34 spoiled by camera malfunction.
      - Rehearsal of the Estudiantina de San Pio; Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Chicago, Illinois, June 30 - July 01, 1977, June 30, 1977; July 1, 1977; AFC 1981/004: b51722; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 0-12, group shots of La Estudiantina de San Pio (1909 E. Ashland) on stairs and at rehearsal, led by Brother Michael Seiberlick, OP [Order of Preachers (Dominicans)]; group members include: guitars: Alan Flores, Dalila Flores, Chita Vazquez, Celia Kielminski, Uliser Flores, Corinne Liza, Lydia Toscano, Maria Vazquez, Bob Delgado, Rosario Badillo, Jane Badillo, Rosie Lopez, Sandy Lopez, Tammy Lopez, Eddie Flores; mandolins: Bicky [Ricky?] Vazquez, Arturo Coevas, Cata Martinez; tambourines: Longino Flores, Letty Badillo; Bass: Mayra Flores; accordion and director; Brother Michael Seiberlick, OP; 13-16, demonstration of La Estudiantina de San Pio group's costume; 17-29, at Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Korean dancers performing; 30-37, Filipino dancers performing at the festival.
      - Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival, Chicago, Illinois, July 01, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b51727; Jonas Dovydenas; 36 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-5, at the Civic Center Plaza Ethnic Dance Festival: unidentified dancers; 6-14, 17-26, 28-35, Asian Forum; Shin-Sun-Do, world peace through a program of physical exercise; 15-16, 27-36, audience.
      - Raising Lithuanian-style chapel pole, Chicago, Illinois; Buddhist Temple Street Fair, Racine and Leland Streets, Chicago, Illinois, July 02, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52021; Jonas Dovydenas; 35 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1, raising chapel pole; 2, 7-8, Rev. Algimantas Kezys, SJ, left, Antanas Poskocimas, maker of the chapel pole, right; 3-4, closeup of the chapel pole; 5-6, Antanas Poskicimas, center; 9-20, Antanas Poskocimas (in dark shirt) checking pole; 21, AntanasPoskocimas, left; 22-36, scenes from Buddist Temple Street Fair, Racine and Leland Streets; 22-29, 33, dancing; 30-32, 34-35, audience.
      - Street scenes near Kenmore and Montrose Avenues, Chicago, Illinois; Japanese Buddhist Temple Street Fair, Chicago, Illinois, July, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b52029; Jonas Dovydenas; 38 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-14, Some shade tree car mechanics near Montrose, behind Kenmore; 15-26 Japanese Buddhist Temple Street Fair, W. Leland Ave; 17, fieldworker Chungmoo Choi.
      - Scenes along N. Clark St. between Belmont and Sheffield, Chicago, Illinois, August 06, 1977, AFC 1981/004: b71991; Jonas Dovydenas; 36 35 mm black-and-white film negatives
        Film negative frame numbers, descriptions: 1-36, street scenes along N. Clark St. between Belmont and Sheffield; 11, Latino-style wall mural on Sheffield, at Clark; 17-26, Leo Rodriquez [Rodriguez?] and friends pitching pennies on Sheffield St. at Addison; Cubs Park is visible on the left; 27-end, Korean American children.
    - Hispanic Americans
      - Rehearsal of El Conjunto de Cuerdas Tipicas de Puerto Rico, under the direction of Israel Maldonado, at El Romance Club, 3575 W. Armitage, Chicago, Illinois, June 28, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 169; Jonas Dovydenas; 7 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-4, rehearsal of El Conjunto de Cuerdas Tipicas de Puerto Rico under the direction of Israel Maldonado at El Romance Club, 3575 W. Armitage, Chicago, Pablo Valentin, second guitar, left; Arcadia Otero, on cuatro, right; 5, Arcadio Otero; 6-7, "El Mucaro" (left) and "El Zumbadour" (right).
      - Latino soccer, Montrose Harbor Park, Chicago, Illinois, July 04, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 170; Jonas Dovydenas; 11 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-10, Latino soccer game, Montrose Harbor Park; 11, picnic at soccer game; note: images are underexposed.
      - Along 26th St. between Kedzie and Pulaski, in the predominantly Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, August 13, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 171; Jonas Dovydenas; 22 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-22, views in the predominantly Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, along 26th St. between Kedzie and Pulaski; 1-5, wall mural; 7-8, front window of grocery, foods advertised in Spanish; 9-12, Little Village Pet Shop with supplementary signs in Spanish; 13-17, Super Mercado La Chiquita food store with painted imagery above door (includes fruits, livestock, and vegetables); 18-20, Carneceria y Fruteria; 21-22, La Victoria (store sign).
      - Along 26th St. between Kedzie and Pulaski, in the predominantly Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, August 13, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 172; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, in the predominantly Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, along 26th St. between Kedzie and Pulaski; scenes include people on sidewalk; 9-13, storefront, signage includes the word "Paleteria;" 14-15, seafood storefront, signage includes "Ostionaria Boca del Rio;" 16-20, window of seafood store.
      - Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, Chicago, Illinois, August 13, 1977, AFC 1981/004: 173; Jonas Dovydenas; 20 35 mm color slide
        Image numbers, descriptions: 1-20, in the predominantly Mexican American Little Village neighborhood, along 26th St. between Kedzie and Pulaski; 1-9, store display windows; 1-2, seafood; 3-9, furniture store windows; 10-13, T-shirt transfer display by street vendor; 14-16, street scene, urban landscape, with bilingual car dealer sign; 17-20, wall mural depicting rural landscape, to suggest Mexico.